[♪ theme music playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[♪ soft nostalgic music playing]
[ice clinking, crackling]
EPISODE 1
[woman vocalizing tune over speaker phone]
[woman] Hold on. Let me start over.
[woman continues vocalizing]
The song that starts like that.
I heard it a few days ago on the radio,
and they said it helps with insomnia.
You said your sleep pattern
has been off lately.
Try listening to it
when you can't sleep. Okay?
This is Seoul.
Boston, please respond.
Hey, engineering student.
Chan.
Hey, Chan!
[♪ soft music continues]
[in English] Is it a gift?
I could engrave it if you'd like.
[sighs]
[team leader in Korean]
The design contest winner is…
Song Haran!
Me? You're kidding, right?
Well, this is unexpected.
The second-year newbie won.
Congratulations, Haran.
-[woman 1] Congrats, newbie!
-Really?
-[man] Congrats! You deserve it!
-[woman 2] Congratulations!
-[Haran] Thank you!
-[laptop pings]
I can't believe it!
Chan! Chan! Chan!
[laptop pings]
The pen you sent me for my birthday…
I used it to draw a design,
and it won in our company contest!
-Let's go!
-[Chan] It won?
[Haran] Thank you so much!
You know,
you're my savior.
[indistinct chatter]
[phone chimes]
[Haran] Hey, it smells like rain.
[rain pattering]
You know that particular smell
before it rains?
I love that smell.
But it disappears so quickly,
so I just stand there smelling it.
[Chan] That's the smell
of organic matter diffusing.
It's called petrichor,
and it's when plant-derived
organic matter spreads--
-[Haran] Hey, nerd. Stop.
-[Chan] The pores in rock crevices…
[Haran] Stop ruining my joy
with science talk, you nerd.
[chuckles]
[Haran] Anyway, smelling the rain
puts me in a good mood.
You should try it sometime.
I recommend it.
[♪ Baroque music playing, J.S. Bach
"Goldberg Variations, BWV 988: Aria"]
[Haran] But the catch is that
you always end up with a nasty cold.
ACHOO!
[inhales deeply]
[sneezes]
[chuckles]
Hey, it's a vapor trail.
[groans] I wish I could get on a plane
and go see Chan.
The boyfriend who's studying in Boston?
I heard Chan's too busy with research
to come during vacation.
Eunchan, you know Haran's boyfriend?
A bit.
He's my little brother.
-What?
-Really?
Let's enjoy our four days off
and work hard for our next season.
[employees] Yes, ma'am!
[employees laugh]
Four days?
[cell phone vibrating]
[Haran panting] Hey, Yujeong!
[Yujeong] We're getting together later.
You free?
Why are you running?
I'm going to Boston to meet Chan.
I'll tell you everything later.
[phone beeps]
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
[laptop pings]
Tsk.
[sighs softly]
[Haran] Chan, I saw a vapor trail earlier.
But that made me want
to get on a plane to go see you.
So…
-Ta-da! I'm at the airport!
-[♪ pleasant music playing]
Isn't that crazy?
I'll have to come back
after only a few hours,
but I wanted
to tell you something in person.
I'll be there at about 1:00 p.m.
in Boston, so just hang in there.
Wait.
I changed my mind.
I'm going to say it now. Hang on.
Chan.
I love you.
I love you, Chan. [chuckles]
[ticking]
[in English] BIT, please.
[♪ pleasant music continues]
5 MINUTES, 0.7 MILES
[gasps, in Korean] Just five minutes left.
[student in English] Hey!
[panting]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[sighs]
[explosion]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[distant explosion]
[sirens wailing, blaring]
[people clamoring]
[cell phone vibrating]
EUNCHAN
[gasps]
Hello?
[Eunchan] Haran, what do I do?
Chan…
[sobbing] Chan is…
[♪ dramatic music continues]
[shuddering]
[high-pitched ringing]
[groans softly]
[exhales]
-[sirens wailing, blaring]
-[people clamoring]
[♪ somber music playing]
[♪ somber music continuing]
SEOUL, SEVEN YEARS LATER
[camera clicks]
[♪ upbeat electronic music
playing on speakers]
Let's begin.
One, two, three.
[cameras clicking]
Awesome.
-[Hayeong] All right.
-Let's take a few more and call it.
Okay.
Excuse me. Coming through.
-Hi.
-Hey. The outfits…
I like how the texture shows here.
[♪ upbeat music continuing]
[cameras clicking]
Nice.
-Nice! You look great.
-[cameraman] Perfect.
Dart. 0.5.
Ms. Kim is here.
[hiccups]
Let's fix the darts by 0.5 inches
before resuming.
Start pinning right away!
Lights.
Dim the backlight by 10%
and adjust the fill lights.
Everyone, move.
-[staff 1] All right.
-[staff 2] Hurry!
Quickly, everyone!
[camera clicking]
All right.
Two, three.
[in English] Okay.
[in Korean] Okay. Great work, everyone.
-Great work, everyone.
-[applause]
The Korean queen of fashion,
the head of Nana Atelier.
Give a round of applause
to our queen, Nana.
[Nana] It's fine.
Clap for the person in charge, not me.
Ah, the person who oversaw it all,
from the outfits to the shoot.
Let's give a hand
to our lead designer, Song Haran!
[employees cheering, applauding]
Excuse me…
I'm sorry, but I don't think she's here.
[chuckles nervously]
[staff] Where did she go?
-She's not here?
-[exclaims]
What's going on?
She was just here.
She even approved the final select shots.
Ghosting…
[groans] She disappeared again,
like always.
[cell phone chimes]
Ms. Song's routine never changes.
[chuckles]
She's like my salary.
She disappears every time.
[Seung-gyu] Right. [chuckles]
[silence]
[♪ Baroque music playing, J.S. Bach
"Goldberg Variations, BWV 988: Aria"]
[sighs]
[indistinct announcement on PA]
Mr. Yeon's coming to our hotel.
The car rental…
Where did he go?
[sighs] Did he wander off again?
[man in English]
Do you guys remember what I just told you?
[group] Yeah!
-[man] Okay, let's go.
-[camera whirs]
[camera ticking]
[♪ pleasant music playing]
[in Korean] What's one plus one?
-[group] Two!
-[in English] Two!
[camera clicks]
[Chan in Korean] Ben, look.
Didn't it come out nice?
[scoffs] I bet
you're the only one in this world
who always makes friends
with everyone on the plane.
You think so?
Mm! [exclaims]
This taste brings back memories.
[exclaims]
When was the last time you were in Korea?
[inhales sharply]
It's been about seven years.
[Ben] Isn't your family in Korea?
Why didn't you come--
Ben. Let's go to Hangang River
after the meeting.
-[laughs]
-No, wait. Maybe Namsan?
Oh!
[in English] I got a list, man.
[in Korean] Okay. Let's look through
my Seoul destinations list.
-First…
-[exclaiming]
No, I can't hear you! I'm going to sleep.
[exclaiming]
Then, I'll have fun by myself.
-Great. Go do that.
-[chuckles]
[breathes deeply]
[♪ sentimental music playing]
I really did come back.
[window whirring]
[wind whooshing]
-[leaves rustling]
-[birds chirping]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Nice to meet you. I'm Yeon Taeseok.
[exclaims] It's nice to meet you,
Mr. Yeon!
I really wanted to see you.
After communicating through just emails,
I knew I'd be happy,
but I can't believe how excited I am.
-Well, I'm not that excited…
-[♪ happy music playing]
Just think of him
like a golden retriever
who loves people. [chuckles]
I see. A golden retriever.
But your Korean is really…
Ah. I'm Ben.
My wife's Korean,
and my in-laws live in Pangyo.
-Ah. Right. Ben.
-[Ben] Yes.
[claps]
Stand over here, Ben.
Let me formally introduce myself.
I'm the one who proposed this project
and a supervisor
with CAN Animation Studio, Seon…
Well, many people get confused,
so let me tell you in advance.
My name's Seonu Chan, not Seon Uchan.
-[Remy] This too?
-[Hayeong] Mmm-hmm.
Wait. Hang on. I can't carry this alone.
[in English] You can do it, baby.
-[staff 1 in Korean] Great work, guys.
-[staff 2] Great job.
-[staff 3] Great work, everyone.
-[staff 4] Good job.
After checking if we have everything,
let's clean up and go.
We should go now
if we want to make it to the afterparty.
[Sol] What's going on?
I guess Ms. Song didn't arrive first.
-I should text her to come to the party.
-[Remy in English] Stop!
[in Korean] Sol, our rookie intern.
You're still clueless about her.
Honey, have you ever had lunch
with Ms. Song before?
-Yes or no?
-No, never.
She always leaves first during lunchtime,
so she must be busy meeting people.
-Not at all.
-Every day, all the time.
Do you think it makes sense
to always have plans?
Gosh. Are you saying
she's avoiding us on purpose?
That's right. [chuckles]
She loves to brood on her own.
She really isn't my vibe.
[sighs] Where is she
always disappearing to?
[♪ serene music playing on speakers]
[sighs contentedly]
PARK GENIUS
-[automation in English] Two points.
-[exclaims]
Three points.
[game buzzes]
-Three points.
-[exclaims]
-[♪ lighthearted music playing]
-[arcade sounds]
[exclaims]
-[camera clicks]
-[in Korean] I got it!
It looks so good.
Mmm.
CHAN SENT PHOTOS
-[cell phone pinging]
-[groans]
[sighing]
[pinging stops]
[in English] Oh, God.
[sighs]
[in Korean] What sort of Korean
enjoys Korea this much?
[♪ lighthearted music continues]
[camera clicks]
[♪ serene music playing on speakers]
[machine thudding loudly]
Sorry about that.
The ice machine
is acting up today. [chuckles]
Be quiet.
Quiet!
Good boy. [chuckles]
This is AI.
[chuckles]
Oh, those.
If you're interested, check them out.
One of my regulars here
organized an exhibit,
and they're showing paintings
for each season.
You can take a bunch of those
and go with friends.
One is enough. Thank you.
Ah. Really?
Going by yourself will be nice, too.
RADIANT SEASONS
[♪ pleasant music playing]
[receptionist] Proceed through
the four seasonal rooms in order.
Okay.
"SHIM"
Coffee House
SPRING ROOM, THE WONDER OF LIFE
WINTER ROOM, DEEP SILENCE
[music fades]
[footsteps]
[clicks]
[chuckles softly]
[guide on headphones] A lone woman
stands with her back turned
in a white, snowy landscape,
quietly conveying
a sense of sorrow and emptiness.
Rather than sharp tension,
the artist's brush captures
the gentle air
and subtle tremble of light.
[♪ soft emotional song playing]
No way…
[Haran] Chan.
I love you, Chan.
[♪ soft emotional song continuing]
[Chan exclaims]
I'm sorry.
[panting]
You idiot.
What will you do if it really is her?
[song fades]
[♪ soft surreal music playing]
[music fades]
[hammering echoes]
[saw whirring]
-[rattling]
-[♪ tense music playing]
-[wood clanks]
-Huh?
Hey, watch out.
-[metal creaks]
-Watch out!
Song Haran!
-[crashing]
-[women scream]
-[exclaims] Are you okay?
-[frantic chatter]
That was close.
-Are you all right?
-[women gasp]
-[woman] Gosh. That was close.
-[breathing shakily]
[man] Are you okay?
[woman] Should we call emergency services?
[man] Are you all right?
-[woman] Are you okay?
-[man] Are you okay?
-Come quickly!
-[Haran] Yes, I'm okay.
-[woman] Are you okay?
-[man] Is anyone hurt?
[man 2] Get down here!
-[man 1] Are they okay?
-[man 2] It's dangerous.
You should all come down.
-[woman] That was so close.
-[man] Come on.
[♪ pleasant music playing]
[Ben on phone] Hey, Too Much.
Why is a Korean so busy touring Seoul?
Right?
Maybe I overdid it.
I fled seven years ago
because I thought I'd see her
everywhere I went.
Seoul seems so big,
but it was actually really small.
Are you saying it's big or small?
Hey, Chan.
Did something happen?
Mmm…
Something did happen…
[chuckles]
but I'm going to pretend it didn't.
I'll think about this today
and forget about it tomorrow,
so don't worry and go to bed.
Bye.
[phone clicks, beeps]
[smacks lips]
[sighs]
[pen scratching]
RADIANT SEASONS
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[Chan] Song Haran!
-[crashes]
-[women scream]
I'm sure they called my name.
Who was it?
Of the three, I'm in charge of designing
and planning the Korean character… [sighs]
CHARACTERS
NIA, WON, FIN
[inhales sharply] Just think of me
as the guy in charge of Won.
[Ben] To highlight the identities
of each character,
we planned collaborations
with designers from each country.
[Chan] I made the collaboration offer
because I really wanted you
to design the Korean character's outfits.
What do you think, Ms. Kim?
Ms. Kim?
So why should I do this?
[Chan] I was curious.
To be honest, I was excited.
I thought your roots
were similar to Won's.
Won isn't someone who shines like the sun.
Instead, she gives light
to those in the darkness,
like the moon.
"Douceur lunaire."
[♪ pleasant music playing]
[mouthing] What's that?
"Soft moonlight."
The first collection you put out
when you were 22.
I saw it myself.
You reinterpreted Korean traditional silk
through moonlight.
You saw it yourself?
It was on display at the fashion school
you attended in France.
Thanks to you,
I got to see the Eiffel Tower, too.
So, what if you expressed Won
with roots like that?
[exclaims]
Just imagining that made me so excited.
So?
What should we do first?
[in English] Yes!
[mouthing] Unbelievable.
Then, let's take a selfie first
to celebrate this day.
Sorry, but you really shouldn't…
Was I being rude, by any chance?
Very rude.
You know,
my left side is prettier.
Then, I'll take one from the left.
One, two, three.
[camera clicks]
Should we show you the story reel first?
-The video will be pretty helpful.
-Sure.
The USB is in my car,
so I'll go and get it.
[door closes]
CHARACTER "WON"
[Nana] It's strange.
-She looks familiar.
-[Ben] Pardon?
It's an original character
that Chan created.
No…
I'm sure I've seen that face before.
[elevator dings]
[humming]
[humming continues]
Hmm?
[sighs]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Huh.
[footsteps echoing]
[Nana] Ms. Song.
Right.
This character looks like
our lead designer, Song Haran.
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
[echoing] I'm sorry.
I dropped my pen by accident.
May I help you?
[echoing stops]
Are you here for the collaboration?
No…
Oh.
Yes, I am.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Song Haran, the lead designer.
[sighs]
[mutters] "It's nice to meet you"?
-Excuse me?
-Right.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Seonu Chan.
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
My pen…
Ah… Here.
Thank you.
Do you have something to say?
No.
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
NANA ATELIER DESIGNERS
LEAD DESIGNER SONG HARAN
[sighs]
Hey, Chan.
-What happened to you?
-It's fine.
[knock on door]
[door closes]
[Haran] I'm sorry.
My prior engagement
ran longer than expected.
No need for excuses.
Say hello.
This is Lead Designer Song Haran,
who will be the main support
for this collaboration project.
She'll be working with you
for the entire three months.
Let's continue.
[Ben] Then,
let's watch the story reel together.
[Nana] Wait.
Mr. Seonu.
That character.
Was it based on someone?
No, it just came to mind.
My grandmother…
I mean, Ms. Kim said that
Won resembles my sister…
[groans]
I mean, Lead Designer Song Haran.
[both exclaim]
-Ooh!
-[in English] Oops.
[in Korean] I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I…
I can't stand those messy clothes.
-Remy, get him a new shirt.
-[Remy] Yes, ma'am.
We'll resume in 10 minutes.
[Remy] Why don't you wait
in the fitting room?
I'll pick out a pretty shirt for you.
It's on the fourth floor.
-[Chan] I'll do it.
-[Hayeong] No, it's fine.
It's all right.
Just head to the fourth floor.
-[sighs]
-[footsteps approaching]
Can you deliver this to the animator?
[chuckles]
I mean, seeing you
brooding like this by yourself again…
You look [in English] very, very…
[in Korean] free right now. [chuckles]
[Remy chuckles]
[sighs]
[sighs heavily]
[♪ soft pensive music playing]
I'll leave your shirt here.
-[exclaims]
-[groans]
I'm sorry! You weren't answering.
Right.
[sighs] Ah…
Here's your shirt.
Thank you.
[sighing]
[♪ soft pensive music continuing]
[door closes]
What's with you today?
You've been acting weird…
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Ben.
I'm stepping out of this project.
[exclaims in English] What?
[in Korean] You stick to the schedule.
I'll head back to the US.
This isn't funny, Chan.
I'll call you as soon as I find
a replacement supervisor.
What on earth…
[in English] Are you serious right now?
You know the director's coming here
with the EA team soon, right?
Hundreds of people have been working
on this project for years
because they believed in you.
Not to mention the expenses.
[in Korean] Seonu Chan.
The Seonu Chan I know wouldn't do this.
No, he can't.
Tell me the reason.
[♪ tense music playing]
Because I'm scared.
I shouldn't be here.
What do you mean?
[in English] Sorry, Ben. Not now.
Let's talk about it later, man.
[in Korean] You said
drawing made you so happy.
When you became a supervisor,
you asked me to smack you
because it felt like a dream.
[in English] Now I see
just how little it really means to you.
[in Korean] Fine. Go.
I don't need a supervisor
who gives up so easily on his work.
[door opens, closes]
[sighs]
WON COSTUME COLLABORATION PROPOSAL
[sighs heavily]
Memento mori…
[ticking]
[in English] He sure left quick.
[cell phone vibrating]
Morning, Ben. How are you?
Wait, actually. It's probably
nighttime there, right?
-[chuckles]
-Anyway, I was just wondering
how the first meeting went
for the fashion collaboration.
Uh, yeah, it went well, but…
Before we get into that,
there's been a bit of an issue with Chan.
-Um…
-Hey, am I late?
Sorry. I was taking a shower.
I thought I should get dressed
before hopping on.
Let's share it.
-Okay.
-[Chan sighs]
Okay, um…
I've sent the materials to Ms. Kim,
and we're meeting in a couple of days
to discuss the concept.
[director] All right. Sounds great.
-Right?
-Yeah. Yeah. That's right. Uh…
-[in Korean] Seonu Chan.
-Yeah?
-What was that?
-What?
Your clothes were gone.
Oh. I dropped them off at the cleaners.
They were all crumpled.
-Let's go get some soy-marinated crabs.
-Soy-marinated crabs?
It's midnight.
[sighs]
Don't you know shops are open
24 hours a day in Korea?
We need to eat well
in order to work hard, you know.
-Right, Producer Ben?
-Seonu Chan.
-You're buying.
-No, I'm not. Last one out is buying.
[Ben exclaims]
[door opens, closes]
[sighs]
[♪ pensive music playing]
[clicks tongue]
Three months…
Just three months.
[sighs] I'm sure nothing will happen.
[door opens]
[door closes]
-[wind whooshes]
-[papers rustling]
[camera whirring, clicking]
[♪ suspenseful music plays]
[camera clicking, whirring]
[thudding]
-[door opens, closes]
-[Hadam] Grandma.
-[Nana] Hey.
-I'm here.
How was your day?
Mmm. It was tough.
It's hard being a high school senior.
But…
Ta-da!
I got a perfect score
after all that studying.
Gosh, you did a great job. [chuckles]
These brains and these looks.
I got so many good genes
from you, Grandma.
[Nana chuckles]
But what did I say
was just as important as studying?
Managing my health.
Here.
I've been taking the tonics
that Mr. Yeon gave me to help me focus.
-[chuckles]
-I'll go get some rest.
Good night, Grandma.
Good night.
[sighs]
How are you busier
than a high school senior?
Where on earth have you…
Forget it. Go upstairs.
Good night.
[sighs]
[knock on door]
Why leave your perfectly fine room
and go into that cave?
Come to my study.
What?
Don't make me repeat myself.
Meet Photographer Yoon.
He's been interested in you
for a long time.
He's talented and has great character.
Someone like that is rare.
Give him a chance.
-No, I'm not interested in dating--
-I know.
Just change your mind.
I'll set a date, so meet with him.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
FAREWELL TO MY FORMER LIFE
[♪ soft emotional music continuing]
[sighs]
-[wind whooshing]
-[birds chirping]
[footsteps approaching]
[grunts]
Good morning.
"Good morning"?
When did you get home last night?
Just a little after midnight.
I suddenly got a bunch of plans.
[sighs] Why is everyone
in this household so extreme?
I wish I could mix the two of you.
-What? Me and who?
-[sighs]
[snores]
My lonely eldest sister?
[Hayeong scoffs]
[reporter]
At a construction site in Seoul,
a large tower of scaffolding
begins to tilt toward the sidewalk.
The scaffolding was a second away
from falling on a woman passing by.
[♪ amusing music playing]
What's with all this fuss again?
[reporter continues speaking]
[TV beeps]
What are you doing?
Well…
[sighs]
I'm trying to protect
my beautiful grandmother's skin
from all the electromagnetic waves.
It's a display of touching devotion
from your second granddaughter.
[chuckles nervously]
I'll go get ready for work now.
-[thuds]
-[groans]
She still hasn't sobered up yet.
Haran!
What? Where is she?
Are you in there again?
Come out here right now!
What is it?
[whooshes]
What?
This woman passing by who almost
got hurt at a construction site.
This is you, isn't it?
It is.
-[grumbles]
-What?
Even I was startled by this.
What if Grandma had seen this?
Please, keep your head on straight
when you're outside. Okay?
I'll keep that in mind.
[Hayeong sighs]
[reporter on phone]
The woman stopped just in time
when someone urgently called her name.
Fortunately, that stopped
-what could've been a terrible…
-Hang on.
What?
This shirt…
[both exclaim]
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Wow. If it weren't for him,
you would've been a goner.
-Hmm? That shirt…
-You recognize it too, right?
Yeah. We remember every color
and texture that people wear.
Isn't that…
the animator's shirt?
-It is. He wore it at the meeting.
-What on earth?
Then, does that mean he was passing by
and shouted when he saw
that you were in danger?
He called out my name.
That's before we even met.
What? How did he call you by your name
when he doesn't know it?
Ah. I get it.
He must be someone in the industry
who knows you.
You're known for your looks.
Plus, plenty of people
wear the same clothes.
You think so?
That's the only way it makes sense.
So who could this savior be?
Right?
Who could it be?
[Sol] Oh. Hello, Ms. Song.
[Seung-gyu] Good morning.
-[in English] Hi.
-[Remy in Korean] Hello.
[beeps]
[knock on door]
Yes?
Ms. Song, the black dress sample is here.
The measurements are perfect.
Let's see it on a mannequin…
I'll wear it.
That will be easier to check.
-Okay. Thanks.
-No problem.
WORK ORDER
Oh?
Ms. Song.
What's with this men's shirt?
Just give that to me
and change into the dress.
[Sol] Okay.
[door closes]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[sighs] I'm sure it's the same shirt.
[Hayeong] Plenty of people
wear the same clothes.
[sighs]
The art exhibit.
RADIANT SEASONS
I went to the exhibit
on the day of our lookbook shoot…
It was the 16th.
He was at the exhibit
on the same day as me.
Then…
he really was the one who called my name?
SEONU CHAN
Seonu Chan.
Seonu Chan…
[♪ suspenseful music continuing]
[sighs]
It doesn't ring a bell.
How did he know my name?
[sighs]
SEONU CHAN
[ice crackling]
[Haran] It's nice to meet you.
I'm Song Haran, the lead designer.
Chan. Chan.
I love you.
I love you, Chan.
[EKG beeping]
[explosion]
[gasps]
[♪ soft pensive music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
[Remy screams]
[Sol] Ms. Song.
-Something weird was delivered to you.
-What a nutjob.
What are you going to do?
I'm the one who received this delivery.
I'm going to be traumatized
after seeing something that sickening
with my pretty eyes.
Do you have any idea
who could've done this?
Not at all.
[Sol] Did you have a bad breakup recently?
Those kind of exes turn into stalkers--
It's fine. This is a personal matter.
Please get back to work.
We don't know what these weirdos
might do if we leave them be.
He's right. A crazy stalker like this
could pop out of nowhere and do something…
Thanks for your concern,
but I'll deal with it myself.
-[Seung-gyu] We're just worried…
-[Sol] Ms. Song…
-[remote beeps]
-[Sol exclaims]
[exclaims] That darned glass.
She's always turning it…
[whimpers] My pretty hands…
What kind of crazy jerk would do this?
Hang on…
[running]
[door opens]
[Hayeong] Haran. I mean, Ms. Song
since we're at work.
The stalker who sent those photos…
Maybe it's the same guy
who called your name in the street.
Right, ma'am?
He could've been following you,
and he could've yelled your name
by accident when you were in danger.
-If you're done, get back to work.
-Work isn't important right now.
[sighs]
All right, Ms. Song.
-What are you doing?
-There's a smudge on it.
Just a second.
I'll excuse myself.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Haran] If the stalker who sent the photos
is the same guy who called my name…
Seonu Chan?
[♪ pensive music playing]
[soft bark]
WON CHARACTER CONCEPT
[Hayeong] Ms. Kim said that
Won resembles my sister…
I mean, Lead Designer Song Haran.
[Haran] If the character
is based on the type of girl he likes,
maybe he saw that I looked similar
when he came to Korea
and learned my name after stalking me.
Then, he followed me to the art exhibit
and witnessed the accident.
I bet he didn't know
we'd be working together.
[gasps]
Is that why he reacted like that?
Right.
It's…
It's nice to meet you.
[Haran] It's because it wasn't
his first time seeing me.
-[scoffs]
-Emergency ice water for you.
You seemed frustrated
about something. [chuckles]
The ice machine
stopped acting up. [chuckles]
One of my regulars who's really handy
dropped by and fixed it instantly.
Thank you.
[cell phone buzzes]
[Nana] There's an urgent meeting
with a client.
Come to Grand Lumiere Hotel
by 7:00 p.m. tonight.
WON CHARACTER CONCEPT
[scoffs]
"SHIM"
Coffee House
[hums, grunts]
[sighs]
-[customer] Hello.
-Hey!
My VVIP regular who fixed my ice machine.
Come on in. [chuckles]
[in English] Welcome.
[in Korean] Hi, Genius.
Here. Sit down.
I'll make you some coffee.
Okay. Thank you.
Genius, wait.
[whines]
[Manjae] Did you go to the art exhibit?
You said you'd go right away
when I gave you the ticket.
Uh…
Yes. Thank you for the ticket.
But for someone
who always smiles so handsomely,
why do you look so gloomy today?
-[chuckles]
-Uh… [inhales sharply]
[exclaims] Right?
I'm usually really handsome,
but I didn't get much sleep,
so I guess I look less handsome today.
Why didn't you get much sleep?
Did you have a nightmare?
[chuckles]
[breathes deeply]
[Chan] Oh.
Do you play the harmonica?
Oh, that. [chuckles]
I found it while cleaning out my clutter.
I get out of breath easily now,
so my chest hurts.
I can't play it so well anymore.
-Here.
-Thank you.
I used to play that often
in my neighborhood when I was little.
Where's your hometown?
Chuncheon.
All I did was find one old object,
but it reminded me of my old hometown
and my childhood friends.
It came with a full package
of old memories. [chuckles]
Memories…
[clicks tongue]
are kind of like sausage links.
What? Sausage links?
Yes.
Even if you think
you've forgotten everything,
recalling just one memory…
seems to bring everything else along.
Like sausage links.
Hey.
Wait just a moment.
-Okay.
-Hang on.
[creaking]
[♪ playing Baroque music, J.S. Bach
"Goldberg Variations, BWV 988: Aria"]
[♪ Baroque piano music continuing]
[lively chatter]
What kind of meeting is it?
I should at least know…
I told you I'd set you up
on a date with Photographer Yoon.
No.
If that's what this is, I'm not attending.
I'm sorry.
How long do I have to see you
act like this?
It's been seven years.
Everyone gets back up and lives
after going through immense pain.
You're the only one who refuses to.
Are you going to keep running away
from everything like a coward?
You can survive
with at least one person to rely on.
But with no one, you'll crumble.
Mr. Yoon can be someone like that for you.
He's a good man, so--
I don't need a good man!
How can you…
Of all people, how can you do this to me?
I'm the one who wants to live like this.
I feel comfortable this way.
I know, okay?
I know I shouldn't live like this.
I know I'm being stupid and weird.
But…
I'm too scared.
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
I don't want to end up
being anxious and worried every day
that something might happen
to someone I care about.
So just let me live like this.
If there's no one by my side,
at least nothing bad will happen.
[exhales shakily]
[tires screeching]
Dad! Mom!
Dad! Dad!
Dad! Mom…
Mom, get up! Mom!
Oh, my God!
Help!
No, Mom…
Mom!
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
Haran.
I can't believe what happened. Hmm?
Grandma.
Mom, Dad,
and Chan…
Even Chan is gone.
Chan is dead, too. [sobbing]
Haran, let's go home. Okay?
Chan is dead too, Grandma.
Chan…
Chan is dead, too.
[crying] Grandma…
[cell phone buzzes]
[Nana] At least show Mr. Yoon
some basic courtesy.
[sighs]
[♪ Baroque music playing, J.S. Bach
"Goldberg Variations, BWV 988: Aria"]
[sighs]
[♪ continues playing Baroque music
on piano]
[Chan] Oh.
-I'm sorry. I played without permission.
-[exclaims]
[in English] Bravo! [chuckles]
[in Korean] Will you have
some wine with me?
There's some sediment in this wine,
so let's drink this
after it settles in a bit.
Okay.
By the way, I guess you like Bach.
No.
I just happened to hear about the song.
Someone told me it's good for insomnia.
Seeing your expression,
I'm guessing today's the kind of day
when your memories come flooding back.
From the way they're coming back to me,
I guess I haven't forgotten about them.
-[♪ soft emotional music playing]
-They were just…
buried for a while.
[Manjae] Mmm.
The thing about memories
is that sometimes…
they're really rebellious.
The more you try to forget,
the more vivid they become.
And when you want to remember,
they run away from you.
So don't strain yourself.
Just try leaving them be.
Just like this wine,
memories get cloudy if you disturb them.
But if you leave them be,
they'll eventually become clearer.
[Manjae chuckles]
[♪ soft music continuing]
[chuckles]
All right.
I'll try to just leave them be.
-Let's drink.
-Okay.
[glass clinks]
I'm sorry.
I'll talk to Ms. Kim and make sure
this mistake doesn't happen again.
I came to say that you don't have
to waste your time on me.
[Yoon] Yes, I know.
I know you don't have any feelings for me,
but I really am sincere…
Are you kidding me?
Right. I understand
you don't want to hear it.
But I really am sincere--
I'm sincerely sorry,
but something urgent came up.
-I'll get going. I'm sorry.
-Excuse me?
[stutters] Ms. Song!
What?
Why are you…
Could you say my name?
-What?
-You're the one who called my name
in front of the art museum
on the 16th, right?
I met you for the first time
a few days ago.
How long have you known me?
Tell me how you know me.
What are you hiding?
[Chan] Someone I have to meet…
[♪ soft emotional song playing]
Someone who brought me back to life
and seems to hold…
the keys to my life.
[♪ soft emotional song continuing]
The seasons of life
don't always come in order.
Sometimes, the moment
you feel like it's spring,
a harsh winter suddenly arrives.
Seven years ago,
in the midst of my coldest winter,
she came into my life
like a warm spring breeze.
And now, she's here again.
And that day, we had no idea
whether our future seasons
would be warm like spring
or harsh like winter.
Seonu Chan…
who are you?
[Haran] I love you, Chan.
I love you,
Kang Hyeokchan.
[♪ soft emotional song continues]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
[song ends]
[Haran] Mr. Seonu.
Why are you stalking me?
[Chan] It feels like
it's hard to get close to her.
[Manjae] She never talks about herself.
[Haran] How did you know
I don't like eggplants?
There's another guy who speaks like him.
[Chan] Why does this keep happening?
It's scaring me.
[Haran] What are you doing here?
[Chan] I'm going to live here.
[Nana] They look good together.
Keep an eye on Ms. Song
and Seonu Chan.
[♪ theme music playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park